Kevin Harger

Microsoft Certified Professional/Specialist – Alphaworks Full Stack React Developer

<u>SUMMARY:</u> Developer with many strong technical skills, ability to engage with stakeholders and identify real needs to deliver project on time. Engaging personality and ability to relate and communicate ideas to business staff, engineers, and executives at all levels. Well trained and experienced in industry leading tech-stacks such as HTML/CSS, JavaScript, React, Dynamics 365, GitHub and others. Many years of experience in medical, environmental, energy, retail, B2C, B2B. Diligent, accurate and dependable.

Tele: 415.737.5221

PROGRAMMING / BUSINESS ANALYST TECHNICAL SKILLS

Developer React, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Typescript, Testing	Excellent Communication/People Skills, Work Ethic
GitHub, Figma, Firebase, Asana, Postgres, WordPress, PHPRunner	SBE Integration Consultant
Microsoft Certified Professional/Specialist Dynamics CRM	Business Analyst

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Alphaworks Technology-Bitwise Industries

Feb 2022 – Present

Full Stack React Developer

- Case Study Created a group project to clone an existing website will all APIs, links, Styling etc.
- Case Study Created Horse Racing Web Game using React, CSS, Redux, Node, Express, PHP, Postgres
- Developed several React frontend websites while interfacing with clients of Bitwise Industries
- Utilized React Router 5/6 to create several Single-Page/Multi-Page Applications
- Created various Full Stack applications using Postgres, Express, Node, JS/React, PHP, CSS, HTML

SensiPass (Security 3-FACTOR dynamic digital signature)

Jan 2012 – Feb 2022

Consultant (Analyst/Developer)

- Consulting on business development and project integration (currently Electronic Access Control)
- Web development on various components using React, JavaScript, CSS, WordPress, PHP, MySQL, AWS Lambda
- Helped prioritize and track which projects are implemented in weekly SCRUMs
- Create documentation of systems and processes using wireframe, swim-lanes, use cases, etc.
- Develop Functional Requirements Documents for Amazon Web Services Connectivity Process
- Develop vendor training and certification program including documentation
- Trained interns on software functionality

KaVo Kerr Group (International Dental Manufacturing)

Feb 2016 – Nov 2016

Senior CRM Business Analyst

- Documentation for Sales and Marketing for five companies; Ormco, Pentron, Kerr, Axis Sybron Endo, and Total Care
- Designed business processes and system to support sales teams
- Communicate status and requirements modifications to developers and c-suite management
- Resolve technical issues involving plugins, work flow processes and marketing requirements
- Mobile CRM users support/planning for sales teams
- Design basic dashboards and reports for analysis, KPI's and process improvements using Visual Studio/SSRS, Salesforce, Tableau, Dynamics CRM 2011/2013, Marketing Data Management, HubSpot, Oracle and Data Warehouse, Badger Mobile
- CRM roll outs, releases and upgrades on an Agile 2 week sprint cycle

Ingram Micro -

Jan 2015 – Feb 2016

Senior Business Analyst (Dynamics CRM 2015)

- Senior Business Analyst for Microsoft Dynamics CRM in more than 25 Countries around the world
- Develop baseline CRM implementation
- Develop business and functional requirements documents in Team Foundation Server
- Create UML Use Cases and Wire Diagrams using Microsoft Visio and Screen shots
- Facilitate User Acceptance Testing
- Sales process Gap Analysis for compatibility to MS Dynamics CRM

Guaranty RV - (Recreational Vehicle Dealership)

July 2014 - Jan 2015

CRM Business Analyst

- Provide Functional Requirements Analysis in an Agile development environment
- Design workflow processes to notify sales persons when new inventory matches customer
- Create Entities, relationships, workflow processes
- Create SSRS reports for monthly monitoring of sales activities and best practices
- Create dashboards and SSRS reports that reflect sales performance and activity
- Import inventory and customer databases from previous system
- Develop marketing campaigns for new leads and existing customers

Veolia Environmental Services -

July 2013 - March 2014

Senior Business Analyst

- Migrated Active Server Pages (ASP) and other server applications during corporate acquisition/relocation
- Modified and configured Security Settings, Time reporting system (Kronos), and MSSQL scripts
- Consulted on design and best practices for CRM 2013

Kohl's Stores – March 2012 – June 2013

Senior Business Analyst

- Lead on deployment and migration teams during Windows 7 migration
- Re-designed automation process for migrations
- Project Lead for remediation of more than 3,000 programs for seven departments including Finance, Sales, Marketing, etc.
- Authored technical documentation for knowledgebase articles

WE Energies –

July 2011 – March 2012

Business Analyst - Level 3

- Designed and managed process used by consultants for capturing and loading user profiles on laptops and PC's company wide
- Central point of contact for resolving migration issues/requests/scheduling/execution for Windows 7 Migration Team
- Authored technical documentation for knowledgebase articles

Panatrack Inc. - 2009-2010

Consultant Dynamics CRM

- Installed/Configure Microsoft Dynamics CRM 2011 IFD, DotNetNuke Web Portal Design
- Customize Integration of CRM 2011, Dynamics GP 10 / MS SQL Server
- Designed sales and quoting system, contract, support, and other processes

Technology Supported:

- React, JavaScript, PHP, PostgreSQL, CSS/HTML
- Microsoft Dynamics CRM 4, 2011, 2013, 2015, 365
- Visual Studio / Code 2022
- SQL Server 2008/2012
- Office 2010/2013/2019

- VPN/DNS, Active Directory
- Windows Desktop V. 1.0 thru V. 11
- PowerShell , Linux (CentOS)
- HubSpot, Salesforce, Outreach
- Windows Server 2008/2012

EDUCATION, TRAINING, Certifications

- AS-Electronic Technology Communications, Milwaukee Area Technical College, Milwaukee, WI
- BS-MIS Computers, Milwaukee School of Engineering, Milwaukee, WI
- Small Business Management and Entrepreneurship, UW Madison, Madison, WI ... Certification
- Computer Science CS50 Harvard University Online ... 2021
- Microsoft Dynamics CRM 2013 ... Microsoft Specialist ... Certification # E816-7969
- Microsoft Certified Professional ... Certification # E816-7970
- Microsoft Windows Server 2012, 2008R2, ... Certified Training
- Microsoft Office 2007, 2010, 2013 ... Certified Training
- Microsoft SQL Server 2012, Exchange 2013, SharePoint 2013 ... Certified Training
- Dale Carnegie Leadership Training for Managers Certification 1997
- ITIL Foundations Training 2016
- BetterUp Whole Person Coaching Program ... 2021
- Bitwise Solutions Programing Bootcamp HTML/CSS/JavaScript ... 2021
- Alphaworks Technology React Developer Federal Registered Apprenticeship Program ... 2022